mytickets.com.au 2010-12-06

# Privacy + Legal | Lasttix | Discount Tickets | Cheap Tickets | Theatre Tickets | Concert Tickets | Musical Tickets & More | Lasttix.com.au

## Maintaining your privacy

Tickets Pty Ltd owns and operates this site 'Lasttix.com.au'. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to maintaining the privacy and accuracy of your personal information. We take all reasonable precautions to ensure the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate and current. However, the accuracy of that information depends largely on the information you provide.

## Collecting personal information

Lasttix.com.au collects aggregated, non-personal statistical information on site visitors such as:

  * your server's address;
  * your top level domain name;
  * the date and time of your visit to the site;
  * the pages you accessed and the documents downloaded;
  * the duration of your visit to the site;
  * the previous site you have visited; and
  * the type of web browser you are using.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information sent to your browser to authenticate, track, and maintain specific information about your interactions with a site. Lasttix.com.au uses cookies to allow you to use specific services such as Lasttix Alerts (a service which sends you event information by email or SMS) to remember who you are if you choose Auto Login and to remember your geographical location for personalised homepages. The type of information we collect depends on what services you sign up for.

You can instruct your browser to refuse cookies, although this may prevent access to or limit some of our services.

## Registration

Registration for Lasttix.com.au services is completely optional. All information provided when registering for Lasttix.com.au services including name, address, and email address can be viewed, modified or deleted at any time by going to the 'User Account' area of the site.

## Using personal information

Lasttix.com.au does not use or disclose your personal information for a purpose other than that for which it was collected, unless such use or disclosure would be reasonably expected or you give us your consent.

We may also collect personal information about you when you purchase tickets, vouchers, merchandise or other products from us or our partners. This information would usually be collected for the purpose of giving effect to the transaction.

## Your personal information may also be used to:

  * market products, services and special offers to you;
  * verify your identity;
  * assist you to subscribe to any newsletter or other promotions we offer or may in the future offer and to manage and administer those services;
  * make changes to your profile;
  * respond to any queries or feedback you may have;
  * inform you of ways the services provided to you could be improved;
  * research and develop our services;
  * maintain and develop our business systems; 
  * gain a better understanding of your information service requirements; and
  * conduct appropriate checks for credit-worthiness or fraud.

## Disclosing personal information

We may use third-party advertising companies (such as DoubleClick and Accipiter) to serve ads on our web site. These companies may use information (not personal or contact details) about your visits to this web site to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## Links to third party sites

Lasttix.com.au contains links to third party sites. These linked sites are not under our control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites and do not know whether cookies or other tracking devices are used on linked sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of each site you visit before disclosing your personal information.

## Securing your personal information

All personal information held by Lasttix.com.au is stored on secure servers that are protected in a controlled environment. You should be aware however that due to the open nature of the Internet, information exchanged via the Internet may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. If you provide or send us any personal information, it is sent at your own risk. Although we endeavour to keep your personal information secure, Lasttix.com.au will not be held responsible for any unauthorised access and use of your personal information.

To help us keep your personal information secure, you should at all times keep your password and accounts used on the Lasttix.com.au site confidential. If you become aware of unauthorised usage of your account you should contact us immediately.

## Privacy changes

To keep this information current and accurate, Lasttix.com.au will review and update this Privacy Policy and post the changes here.

## Contact us

Please contact us to find out more about our procedures and policies in relation to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and handling of personal information.  
If at any time you wish to know what information we are holding about you, think we may hold information about you which is incorrect / out of date, you request we delete your personal information, or link(s); you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us on:

Email: [support@Lasttix.com.au](mailto:support@Lasttix.com.au)  
Phone: 1300 TICKETS  
Post: User Help Desk  
Lasttix.com.au  
Level 10, 45 Market Street Sydney NSW 2000  
Australia 

If you still require further information then you should contact the Office of the Federal Privacy Commissioner whose details follow:

Phone: Privacy Hotline on 1300-363-992; or   
Web: [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/ "www.privacy.gov.au")   
Post: The Federal Privacy Commissioner  
GPO Box 5218  
Sydney NSW 1042.
